http://www.presbox.com/privacy-policy

PresBox US Privacy Policy
Presentation Box + Display (US) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any personally identifiable information we ask you to provide when using this website will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
This privacy policy explains how we use any personal information we collect about you when you use this website.
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you register with us or place an order for products or services. We also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions. Website usage information is collected using cookies.
How will we use the information about you?
We collect information about you to process your order, manage your account and, if you agree, to contact you about other news, products and services that we think may be of interest to you. We may use your information collected from the website to personalize your repeat visits to our website.
We will never pass your personal information to any third party, other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, but reserve the right to access and disclose personal information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests; requests by the police investigating suspected illegal activities; to enforce our website terms and conditions; and to operate our systems properly, administer the website, or to protect ourselves or other website users. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Marketing
We would like to send you information about products and services which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date.
You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. When you input any personal information into the website, we will use appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial security measures to try to prevent this personal information from being accessed by unauthorized persons, and to ensure that you may input personal information safely. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.
Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk.
Access to your information and correction
You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..
We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.
Cookies
Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information.
We use cookies for the following:
To deliver specific functionality to the user allowing the website to work properly
To gather anonymous data on user behaviour on the website so that we can better understand user journeys and improve the website as a consequence
For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org.
You can set your browser to not accept cookies. The above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in some cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.
Other websites
Our website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website, so be sure to read the privacy policy of other websites for more information about their specific policies.
Changes to our privacy policy
We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on June 26, 2019.
How to contact us
Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy or information we hold about you:
By email at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
By mail at 517 Mineral Spring Ave, Pawtucket, RI 02860
US 800 556 7390About UsFlexShip™Quick-Ship™Digital CatalogFlexShip/Program LogIn
International PackagingMason BoxJewelryPackaging.comShow SpecialHeritage Info Sheet
ContactPrivacy PolicySite Index©PRESBOX 2017
